你好，漂亮的人们欢迎收看这个视频，在这里你们将学习如何复制和粘贴
Hello you beautiful people are welcome to this video where you're going to learn how to copy and paste
使用命令行创建文件和文件夹。
files and folders using the command line.
现在，这应该是一个很好的、快速的讲课，只有一个命令。
Now this should be a nice and quick lecture with just one command.
在Linux中处理所有文件和文件夹复制的C.P.命令。
The C.P. command which handles all the copying of files and folders in Linux.
在视频结束时，您将了解如何使用命令行和
By the end of the video you'll know how to copy and paste files and folders using the command line and
您还将了解如何将C-p命令与通配符配合使用，以使复制和粘贴更加出色。
you also see how to use the C-p command with wildcards to make copying and pasting even more awesome.
所以，让我们继续直截了当地谈吧。
So let's go ahead and get right into it.
好的。
OK.
所以我们来了。
So here we are.
正如您在shell提示符中看到的那样，我当前在桌面上，并且在桌面上有一个文件
And as you can see by the shell prompt I'm currently on the desktop and on the desktop I have a file
这里叫做文件1.60，如果我打开它，它会说你好，你们这些漂亮的人。
here called File 1.60 and if I opened it says hello there you beautiful people.
我想知道这是怎么回事。
I wonder how that got there.
假设我们想要将该文件复制到另一个名为file to DR XTi的文件中。
So let's say we wanted to copy that file to another file called file to Dr XTi.
好的，因为我非常非常富有想象力。
OK because I'm very very imaginative.
因此，要复制它，我们使用cp命令，C-p是copy的缩写。
So to copy it we use the c p command and the C-p being short for copy.
现在我们只需要告诉COPY命令。
Now we just need to tell the copy command.
我们要复制的内容以及要复制到的位置。
What we want to copy and where we want to copy it to.
那么我们要复制什么呢。
So what do we want to copy.
嗯，我们想要复制文件1.60。
Well we want have to copy file 1.60.
请记住，我已经在桌面上洗澡了，所以如果我在家里，我可以只写1.60美元
And remember I'm on the desktop already in the shower so I can just write for 1.60 if I was in the home
文件夹，我会说将桌面sosh复制到1.60，只是为了让你知道。
folder I would say copy desktop sosh for 1.60 just just so that you're aware.
好的。
OK.
那么让我们再来一次桌面。
So let's go to the desktop again.
所以我们需要告诉它我们想复制什么，我们想要复制到什么地方。
So we need to tell it what we want to copy and we want to copy it to.
所以我们想要一份1.60的拷贝，我们想拷贝到一个或者叫做“法尔图战术”的文件中。
So we want a copy for 1.60 and we want to copy to one or the file called Faltu tactics.
这就是我们要输入的全部内容，希望将一个文件复制到另一个名为File2.6的文件中，当我这样做时
So that's all we've got to type want to copy far one into another file called File 2.6 and when I do
我们会在这里看到一个叫做法尔图的文件。
that we'll see we get a file here called Faltu.
当我张开嘴的时候，我也会向你们打招呼，你们这些漂亮的人。
And when I open up that also says hello there you beautiful people.
好的。
OK.
这就是如何将一个文件复制到另一个文件，这非常简单。
So that's how you copy a file to another file which is pretty simple.
那么，如何将文件复制到目录的另一个文件夹。
So how would you copy a file to another folder to the directory.
嗯，那也很简单。
Well that's pretty simple too.
正如我所说的复制命令，您所要做的就是告诉它您想要复制什么以及要复制到哪里
As I say the copy command all you've got to do is tell it what you want to copy and where you want to
将其复制到。
copy it to.
好的。
OK.
假设我要将Fall One复制到名为Destination的文件夹中。
So let's say I want to copy fall one into this folder called Destination.
好的。
OK.
所以我要做的就是复制文件一。
So I'll have to do is I copy file one.
到目前为止是1.60，复制到目的地。
So far 1.60 and copy to destination.
也可以说我同时也想复制法尔图。
And also let's say I also wanted to copy Faltu at the same time.
好的，这是一份拷贝，并将Faltu文件放到目标文件夹中。
OK so it's copy for one and file Faltu into the destination folder.
好的，您可以在这里看到，您放在命令行参数中的最后一件事是目的地
OK so you can see here that the last thing that you put as a command line argument is the destination
所有其他的东西都是你想要复制的，所以我可以有很多
and everything else that comes with for that is what you want to copy so I could have many many many
不同的命令。
different commands.
我想在这里复制很多不同的文件，但最后一个是我想要复制它们的位置
And many many different files that I want to copy here but the last one is where I want to copy them
都到了。
all to.
对，是这样。
Correct.
现在，让我们继续按Enter，当我查看Destination内部时，我们可以看到
So with that let's go ahead press enter and when I look inside destination we can see that we've got
四号，一号文件，二号文件。
four one on file two.
他们都被复制进去了。
They have both been copied into that.
如您所见，使用该命令，整个复制和粘贴业务实际上相当简单
So as you can see this whole copying and pasting business is actually rather simple with the command
排队。
line.
当然，您也可以使用通配符。
And of course you can also do it with wild cards.
所以我现在在桌面上。
So I'm on the desktop at the minute.
假设我想删除所有以Word file开头的内容。
Let's say I want to remove everything that starts with the Word file.
因此，如果我这样做，两个文本文件都应该消失，因为它们都以单词file开头。
So if I do that both the text files should disappear because they both begin with the Word file.
所以如果我这么做了，他们是不是都消失了。
So if I do that are they both disappear.
现在我可以将目标文件夹中的所有内容复制并粘贴到桌面，但您是说
Now I can copy and paste all the stuff from in the destination folder to the desktop but you're saying
复制目的地。
copy destination.
劈开应有尽有。
Slash everything.
好的。
OK.
放到这个折叠处。
To this fold.
以及如何选择此文件夹。
And how do I select this folder.
如果你还记得，在每个位置总是有一个隐藏的文件夹，这指的是
Well if you remember back the there's always a hidden folder in each location and that refers to the
文件夹是，如果我只是这样做，那是句号，所以如果我只做那个点。
folder is if I just do and that is the full stops so if I just do that dot dot.
这意味着将目标文件夹中的所有内容复制到此文件夹中，该文件夹是
What that means is copy everything from within the destination folder into this folder which is the
桌面，这就是我们目前所在的游戏。
desktop which is where we currently are the game.
所以如果我这样做，如果我按Enter键。
So if I do that if I press enter.
您将看到文件ONE FILE已被复制并粘贴到此位置，该位置由
You'll see the file one file to have been copied and pasted to this location which is represented by
句号在这里。
the full stop here.
如果你不记得我是不是只用A选项来做l，你可以在这里看到，我们有这两个
And if you don't remember if I just do ls with the A option you can see here that we've got these two
隐藏文件夹和一个文件夹指的是此文件夹，折叠的文件夹指的是双倍文件夹
hidden folders and the one with the one refers to this folder and the one with the doubled up refers
添加到它上面的文件夹，这是我们的主文件夹。
to the folder above it which is our home folder.
好的，例如，我可以将目标文件夹中的所有内容复制到其中的父文件夹
OK so I could for example copy everything from the destination folder to the parent folder of where
我们目前是哪个是主文件夹。
we currently are which is the home folders.
如果我这样做，现在查看我们的主文件夹，我们可以看到在其中创建了一个文件
If I do that and I now look at our home folder we can see the file one file to have been created in
那里。
there.
所以请看，通配符对任何命令都非常有效。
So look wildcards work absolutely great with any command.
甚至复制命令也是如此。
Even the copy command as well.
那么让我们清理一下屏幕。
So let's clear the screen.
我们已经了解了如何将一个文件复制并粘贴到另一个文件中。
We have seen how to copy and paste a file into another file.
我们已经了解了如何将文件复制和粘贴到文件夹中，以及如何从文件夹复制粘贴文件
We've seen how to copy and paste a file into a folder and we've seen how to copy paste files from folders
放到其他文件夹中。
into other folders.
我们唯一需要知道的就是如何复制和粘贴整个文件夹。
The only thing we need to know is how to copy and paste entire folders.
好的，我们在这里。
OK so we have here.
这个复制桌面上的文件夹，里面有三个文件。
This copy the folder on the desktop and that's got three files in it.
里面有法利赫·法比和法西。
It's got Faleh Fabi and falsie.
好的。
OK.
我们希望将整个文件夹复制到目标文件夹中，这样我们不仅需要
And we want to copy this entire folder into the destination folder so we don't just want the files we
文件夹也要，这样我们就不只想要巧克力了。
want the folder as well so we don't just want the chocolate.
我们还想要包装纸。
We also want the wrapper.
好的。
OK.
我们可以这样做的方法是，给C-p命令一个选项，这个选项也代表递归。
So the way that we can do this is by giving the C-p command the option which also stands for recursive.
现在，如果您还记得我们在上几个视频中使用R.M.删除文件和文件夹时的情景
Now if you remember from when we were deleting files and folders in the last few videos with the r.m
选项递归删除意味着删除该文件夹以及其中所有内容。
option recursive deleting meant delete that folder and everything inside it.
这与复制命令非常相似。
And it's very similar for the copy command.
我们要说的是复制文件夹和其中的所有内容。
What we're saying is copy the folder and everything inside of it.
好的。
OK.
因此，要将文件夹的副本实际复制到我们刚才键入的目标文件夹中，我们假设可以
So to actually copy the copy of the folder into the destination folder we just typed out we say could
我们说使用选项进行复制，然后将我复制到目标文件夹，如果我这样做了，我们就会查看
we say copy with the option then copy me into the destination folder and if I do that and then we look
在目标内部，我们将看到Copy Me文件夹已复制并粘贴，并且所有
inside the destination we will see that the copy me folder has been copied and pasted and all of the
不同的文件也在里面。
different files are inside there as well.
一切安然无恙。
All safe and sound.
所以他们拿到了。
So they have it.
现在，您可以使用命令行复制和粘贴文件和文件夹。
You can now copy and paste files and folders using the command line.
这很容易，对吧。
It's quite easy right.
作为非常快速的回顾，您可以看到C-p命令处理文件的复制和粘贴
So as a very quick review you saw that the C-p command is what deals with copying and pasting of files
和Linux中的文件夹，它的工作方式是你有你输入的C.P.。
and folders in Linux and the way that it works is you have the C.P. you type c.p.
然后你想复制什么，你可以想要多少就有多少。
Then what you want to copy and you can have as many of those as you like.
最后，您给它的最后一个命令行参数就是您的目的地。
And then in the end the last command line argument that you give it is your destination.
好的。
OK.
所以你可以有很多你想复制的东西，但是你给它的最后一件事就是单一的目的地
So you can have many things you want to copy but the final thing that you give it is the single destination
你想把这些东西都放到哪里去。
where you want all of those things to go.
现在，如果您想复制整个文件夹，不仅要复制它们的内容，还要复制实际的包装器
Now if you want to copy entire folders so not just their contents but the actual wrapper the actual
文件夹本身。
folder itself.
然后，您需要为copy命令提供允许其递归复制整个文件夹的选项。
Then you need to give the copy command the option to allow it to copy entire folders recursively.
现在有了复制和粘贴，接下来我们要做的是，我们将讨论
And now with copying and pasting and way up next what we're going to be doing is we're going to be discussing
在Linux中移动和重命名文件和目录。
moving and renaming files and directories in Linux.
真正有趣的是，您实际上可以使用一个命令来完成这两件事。
And what's really interesting is that you can actually use just one command to do both those things.
为了学习如何使用一个命令来移动和重命名文件，我将在下一个视频中与您见面。
So to learn how to move and rename files using just one command I'll see you in the next video.